<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ /*******************************************************************************
  ~  * OpenFlightGPS is Copyright 2009-2015 by Roger B. Leuthner
  ~  *
  ~  * This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY;
  ~  * without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
  ~  * GNU General Public License for more details.
  ~  *
  ~  * Commercial Distribution License
  ~  * If you would like to distribute OpenFlightGPS (or portions thereof) under a license other than
  ~  * the "GNU General Public License, version 2", contact Roger B. Leuthner through GitHub.
  ~  *
  ~  * GNU Public License, version 2
  ~  * All distribution of OpenFlightGPS must conform to the terms of the GNU Public License, version 2.
  ~  ******************************************************************************/
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="beta_text">
		OpenFlightGPS is NOT AN OFFICIAL AERONAUTICAL RESOURCE.  All 
		Aeronautical Decision Making must be based upon official resources. 
		DO NOT USE OPENFLIGHTGPS for pre-flight or in-flight
		reference.  FAA resources are minimally processed in order to allow viewing
		on OpenFlightGPS, but some processing does occur.  This processing causes the FAA products
		to deviate from their original, official form and AS SUCH DO NOT USE OPENFLIGHTGPS in any
		official capacity.  By the code in the text input area you are
		agreeing to this restriction and the following license terms:

Definitions
"Developer" shall mean Roger Leuthner.
"Software" shall mean OpenFlightGPS and/or OpenFlight Map, all versions.
"Service" shall mean an online component that the Software interacts with.

Grant of Limited Use License:
The Developer hereby grants the End User a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable license to
(a) install the Software on one or more devices owned by the End User or under End User\'s legitimate control, and (b) use the Software for non-commercial purposes only.

Additional License Limitations:
The license granted to the End User in this document is subject to the limitations set forth in same (collectively, the "License Limitations").  Any use of the Software in violation of the License Limitations will be regarded as an infringement of the Developer\'s copyrights.  The End User agrees not to, under any circumstances:
A.  reproduce or reverse engineer, derive source code from, disassemble, decompile or create derivative works based on the Software;
B. exploit the Software or any of its parts for any commercial purpose;
C.sell or transfer reproductions of the Software to other parties in any way not expressly authorized herein.

Ownership:
All title, ownership rights and intellectual property rights in and to the Software and all copies thereof are owned or licensed by the Developer.  The Software is protected by the copyright laws of the United States of America.  The Software may contain materials licensed by third parties, and the licensors of those materials may enforce their rights in the event of any violation of this License Agreement.

Termination:
This License Agreement is effective until terminated.  The End User may terminate the License Agreement at any time by (I) permanently destroying all copies of the Software in End User\'s possession or control; (ii) removing the Software from the End User\'s device, and (iii) notifying the Developer of End User\'s intention to terminate this License Agreement.  The Developer may terminate this Agreement at any time for any reason or no reason.

Patches and Updates:
The Developer may deploy or provide patches, updates and modifications to the Software that must be installed for the user to continue to use the Software.

The Online Component of the Software:
This Software is an online application that must be used over the Internet through a Service provided by the Developer.  The End User understands and agrees that the Service is provided by the Developer at its discretion and may be terminated or otherwise discontinued by the Developer.

Information Collection:
The Developer is not responsible in any way for data collected by Google, Incorporated or its subsidiaries, or by Internet Service providers that End User may employ to obtain services from The Developer.

Limited Warranty:
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED “AS IS”, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES O MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PUPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS, THE DEVELOPER OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIN, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.

Limitation of Liability, Indemnity:
NEITHER THE DEVELOPER NOR ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR AFFILIATES SHALL BE LIABLE IN ANY WAY FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND ARISING OUT OF THE SOFTWARE OR ANY USE OF THE SOFTWARE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LOSS OF DATA, LOSS OF GOODWILL, WORK STOPPAGE, HARDWARE FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION, OR ANY AND ALL OTHER DAMAGES OR LOSSES.  THE DEVELOPER SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY INTERRUPTIONS OF SERVICE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ISP DISRUPTIONS, SOFTWARE OR HARDWARE FAILURES OR ANY OTHER EVENT WHICH MAY RESULT IN A LOSS OF DATA OR DISRUPTION OFF SERVICE.  IN NO EVENT WILL THE DEVELOPER BE LIABLE TO THE END USER FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.  In no event shall the Developer\'s liability, whether arising in contract, tort, strict liability or otherwise, exceed (in the aggregate) the total fees paid by the End User to the Developer.  The End User hereby agrees to defend, indemnify and hold the Developer harmless from and against any claim, liability, loss, injury, damage, cost or expense (including reasonable attorney\'s fees) incurred by the Developer arising out of or from the End User\'s use of the Software.

Equitable Remedies:
The End User hereby agrees that the Developer would be irreparably damaged if the terms of this License Agreement were not specifically enforced, and therefore the End User agrees that the Developer shall be entitled, without bond, agrees that the Developer shall be entitled, without bond, other security, or proof of damages, to appropriate equitable remedies with respect to breaches of this License Agreement, in addition to such other remedies as the Developer may otherwise have available to it under applicable laws.  In the event any litigation is brought by either party in connection with this License Agreement, the prevailing party in such litigation shall be entitled to recover from the other party all the costs, attorneys\' fees and other expenses incurred by such prevailing party in the litigation.

Changes to the Agreement:
The Developer reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify, add to, supplement or delete any of the terms and conditions of this License Agreement at any time.  The End Users continued use of the software constitutes acceptance of any changes thus made.

End User (You) hereby acknowledge that you have read and understand the foregoing License Agreement and agree that by installing or using the Software you are acknowledging your agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of this License Agreement.

	</string> 
	
	<string name="download_msg">Do you want to download the map?  It will take a long time unless you are
		on WIFI or 3G.  You may continue to run other apps while the download proceeds, but DO NOT use the backbutton
		or the download will fail.  To use other apps, first use the "Home" button then start
		up another app, or an app switcher to go directly to another running app.
	</string>
	
	<string name="compass_enabled_summary">Show compass when \'My Location\' is enabled.  
		Also faces ownship on map in direction device is pointed, rather than (sampled moving) GPS heading. 
		Causes ownship and heading line to display whether you are in motion or stationary; 
		otherwise the (sampled moving GPS) heading line is only shown when movement is detected.
	</string>
	
	<string name="no_more_maps">
		Sorry, your license is exceeded so you can only use maps you already have downloaded.  
		Either upgrade, delete 1 or more maps, or renew your subscription.
		Please refer to \'About\' page for more info.  Thanks for using OpenFlightGPS!
	</string>
	
	<string name="hard_stop">
		Number of maps found exceeds license.  Deactivating GPS features.  Re-enable by opening unneeded maps and choosing the
		\'Delete Map\' menu item for each map over the limit of your license.	
	</string>
	
</resources>
